{
    "id": "c3ccd2653beb4f96a23e262db56f509d",
    "title": "Degrees Of Comparison Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Mount Everest is the …………………….peak in the world.",
            "description": "The superlative indicates the highest degree.",
            "answers": [
                "highest",
                "higher",
                "high"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e8805283d2b24ebebf084c08b6eba7fc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mount Everest is …………………… than any other peak in the world.",
            "description": "We use a comparative adjective before the expression than.",
            "answers": [
                "higher",
                "high",
                "highest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "43331374d5e44c9ca8a8a31a80870baf"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sachin is …………………… famous than any other Indian cricketer.",
            "description": "We use a comparative adjective before the expression than.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "more",
                "most"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "967fa553372241ceb803f45399612c59"
        },
        {
            "question": "Lead is …………………….. metal.",
            "description": "The article the is used before superlative adjectives.",
            "answers": [
                "the heavy",
                "the heavier",
                "the heaviest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "05095ff780784cb18483ebe12d3f3f37"
        },
        {
            "question": "No other metal is as …………………… as lead.",
            "description": "Positive adjectives are used in the construction as …as…",
            "answers": [
                "heavy",
                "heavier",
                "heaviest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "862310ba3b754de59f5a4b7b5334d7c6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mayank is …………………….. than any other boy in the class.",
            "description": "We use a comparative adjective before the expression than.",
            "answers": [
                "tall",
                "taller",
                "tallest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1cd43aa26bdc418b8b05a0a1e4d93a80"
        },
        {
            "question": "The elephant is ……………………… land animal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "big",
                "bigger",
                "biggest",
                "the biggest"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "a59e6fe477614f2993e5dde6e3fdae35"
        },
        {
            "question": "Preeti is …………………… girl in the class.",
            "description": "We use the superlative to compare one person or thing with the whole group to which that person or thing belongs.",
            "answers": [
                "prettier",
                "the prettier",
                "the prettiest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8f2adf380d564844af5eec6a4dab3952"
        },
        {
            "question": "Lotus is …………………….. than any other flower.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "beautiful",
                "more beautiful",
                "most beautiful"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4977dad6d1fe4651b6488f921631991b"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are no …………………….. than me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "better",
                "well",
                "best"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ac071e4e4e1b4291a5de413398d37c30"
        },
        {
            "question": "Bhim was ……………………….. of the Pandavas.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "strongest",
                "the stronger",
                "the strongest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "effa9852b5da41dab16447a7fd50407f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The peacock is one of the ……………………. birds.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more beautiful",
                "most beautiful"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1e34e9ceeac144aba5e27c87bd900e05"
        }
    ]
}